In the season of storms
在風暴的季節裡
Two made it by one, easily
兩人輕易走過一場
In the dawning sunset,
在夕陽西下之際,
At night in the early afternoon, casually
在清晨的夜裡, 從容不迫
No matter how bad our bodies decay We'd love to laugh at the end of time
不管身體多糟糕 我們都想笑到最後一刻
No matter what you're fighting for I want you to be motivated by love
不管你為何而戰 我希望你的動力是愛
No need to look for brand-new days They're always here with us
不需要尋找全新的日子 它們一直都在我們身邊
Though I've seen a lot of things in my life My eyes will always & forever be sparkling
雖然我見過很多事 我的眼永遠閃閃發光
Though I've lived that life so long Everything I've been thru is like a dream
雖然我活了這麼久 我所經歷的都像夢一場
Everything looks attractive But you're the only one for me
一切都那麼吸引人 但你是我的唯一
Where have you been, I've been looking for you
你去了哪裡, 我在找你
Take me there, take me there
帶我去那裡, 帶我去那裡
Giving up everything and going with you
放棄一切 跟你走
To anywhere, To everywhere
去任何地方, 去所有地方
In extreme weather, in a crazy crowd
在極端天氣, 在瘋狂人群中
With you I can go, smoothly smoothly
有你在 我能平穩前行
Our brand-new future, awkward past,
我們嶄新的未來, 尷尬的過去,
Everything will be shiny (Kirari)
一切都會閃閃發亮 (Kirari)
Looking back on what I had to lose
回想著我失去的
...makes me weep
...讓我落淚
Sometimes I'm lost at sea
有時我在海上迷失
Just swaying in the wind, unsteadily
只在風中搖擺, 搖搖欲墜
I came running out of breath
我跑得上氣不接下氣
Already decided where to go
已經決定要去哪裡
I'd rather not get lost but who knows
我不想迷路但誰知道
I thought I knew something
我以為我懂些什麼
In fact I knew nothing
其實我什麼都不知道
But now at least I know it and I'm so glad
但現在至少我知道了 我好高興
No need to look for brand-new days
不需要尋找全新的日子
They're always here with us
它們一直都在我們身邊
here with us, with us, Ah
在我們身邊, 在身邊, 啊
Though I've seen a lot of things in my life
雖然我見過很多事
My eyes will always & forever be sparkling
我的眼永遠閃閃發光
forever be sparkling,
永遠閃耀,
Ah, though I've lived that long Everything I've been through is like a dream
啊, 雖然我活了這麼久 我所經歷的都像夢一場
Everything looks attractive But still you're the only one for me
一切都那麼吸引人 但你仍是我的唯一
Where have you been, I've been looking for you
你去了哪裡, 我在找你
Take me there, take me there
帶我去那裡, 帶我去那裡
Giving up everything and going with you
放棄一切 跟你走
To anywhere, To everywhere
去任何地方, 去所有地方
In extreme weather, in a crazy crowd
在極端天氣, 在瘋狂人群中
With you I can go, smoothly smoothly
有你在 我能平穩前行
Our brand-new future,
我們嶄新的未來,
Our awkward past,
我們尷尬的過去,
Everything will be shiny (Kirari)
一切都會閃閃發亮 (Kirari)